Hi, Samantha. Wow. Crazy people. Thank you so much. I mean, good time to know. I mean,
you know, you just got in trouble for doing that. Oh, why?
Yeah, thank you so much. Thank you so much.
But we'll get back into this way.
Thanks.
What happened? It wasn't me, right? No. Um, he showed fire on me
He told you. Yeah, bro. I told you didn't I call it. I was like psyche throw him down. He's gonna show a gun
You caught it back you caught it and I missed it actually I didn't even see it
I just came back and was gone
I was teasing him a little bit about hey
You know where to come to your house for a party tomorrow
Just you know
It's because he it irritates him and then he's like well
You're not gonna come mother fuckers look and then he has these two like machine guns or something out of
Three across on the chest
If you shut your fucking like blow his own finger off
Have you ever shot his gun like I just blew up fucking hole in my hand like shut up good times
Stop ruin his psyche straight and acting like that. Come on show a little respect
Show a little fucking respect. He's like that really happened that called it fuck
He flashed the piece, I didn't see the do-loader.
but that's a good day in Gulliver
I saw that
we were talking about his overalls
he had like these two
machine guns, like two small machine guns
you know why he's doing that also
they were all machine guns like
they were all machine guns
whatever they were
they were all machine guns, come on
I know that, but they were like
the Tommy guns, they're like little automatic guns
but they're like smaller
They look kind of big. I love wasn't there a fly going around in the party at its house. They were not Tommy Guns
They were not Tommy Guns cobbled
He's Al Capone now
You see a Tommy gun
all he did, he got fucking, he got a fucking big ol' dick
Tommy's gun's a big, a pretty big, Tommy's gun's pretty big
he flashed a piece that he doesn't see either, yep
it didn't do anything
then you could ever imagine
oh wow
yeah but see, in particular the law enforcement
too much to track down his IP
and check out who Goot Times really is
like this is 2025
and they can see if he's even allowed to have those guns
You know
Newsy it was like a fucking machine gun
So he's just fucking himself bro showing that shit
There'll be a swarming at his door in a half hour like really mr. Good
I'll fight you one ball I'll fight you one ball
If I was the king of the forest,
No, if I was the king of the forest,
Put him up, put him up.
But I actually respect Alex since he knew the Caroline song site that notion. I know I know
I think it all the time when I go to the park. I got a jump on a bench and I do it
It's not my favorite
Let me say one last thing about Wizard of Oz one of my favorite scenes is when
Dorothy and them come out of like getting scrubbed up like scrub scrub
Yeah, and then in the sky that which is like surrender Dorothy. She's like, oh my god
She's in the sky
That's beat up. That was beat up. I was a kid. I cried. I was like, no
That's fucking beat up bro. She looks exactly like it
It's when be the melts when they put them
I actually used to have Christmas the fuck out of you boy
I used to have a Christmas on my tree, you know, the ornaments.
I had a Wizard of Oz ornament that was the monkey's prong and the witch would come down.
I'm melting, I'm melting.
That was what...
Can I say one thing with Psyche, please?
And Alex, you can hear this, but let me talk to Psyche before he bans me.
I remember when I was in fourth grade, they did a thing with the teachers like you got
to buy your classmate a gift and your other classmate will buy you a gift.
And I remember my friend Sean, no, no, hold on.
My friend Sean and Sean, they both were named Sean.
They got each other.
They bought each other baseball cards and I was like, oh, it's fucking, hey, my, I got
my friend, Jamie Miller.
She wasn't even my friend.
She was just like a fucking women.
No, she was like fucking.
The point I'm trying to make is that that ornament still hangs on my tree and I think about every
Christmas when I see that ornament I think about Jamie and you know when I was a kid
I hated getting that gift but now that I'm older
God bless him because either I was dreaming or I said I had a dream that I'm a lover page.
I love it. I love it. I love it.
So I told the race.
Let me tell you one thing, Alex, Alex, look at me and listen to me.
I swear to God the other day, I had a dream that I was hanging out with Good Times and
Aldi and Drusky and we were chilling off.
And then I was like in a high school and I see Manette and I was like, Manette, we got
to put this teddy bear somewhere.
and then i woke up and i was like damn that sucks that i woke up because i will fucking i would
love to do anything for a minute that's what i mean exactly really good looking women if i got
when you ate coffee like fuck i was about to fuck that bitch like go back go back to that dream
thank you man you know what i'm talking about exactly what's happening to me
That's funny
Talk to Manette, but I know you can't you can't go back to the same
I know I know she has she's been on she's been in my chat before and she's on that B2
I know she had a dream a female chatter and saw me with like this
Lady gone
I hope you had to put somewhere and man that was like and like somebody in the class was like it don't belong here
You got to put it down the basement. I looked at Manette's like you want to put in the basement. She's like I'm on
we have fun. I had a dream. Hold on. Let me read that. Or read that out loud. It's like, please, read that.
I had a dream.
They're not only just dreams, they're messages. We don't even know what they are, though.
Yeah, but it feels so real.
Brian, he was just, he was putting them in a menacing way, like, you know, even though they were like, he was like this, like, one of those poses, like that.
I have a dream of you dreaming of somebody, that person that's dreaming about you, too, or thinking about you.
You're like electrical energy is all connecting
One thing about me and I throw my camera on some very serious about this
I felt so bad the other day when I got clipped and I was arguing with Bita because I have no
Harfields of Bita. She's one of the coolest motherfuckers and I never want to attack Bita
And I was just getting drunk and like being an asshole. So Bita's out there. I apologize, sweetheart
I got to my camera. So we're crying
Okay, well
Y'all say things you regret sometimes
Princess lay in the middle look at them Princess psyche layer look at them
by the way when I had a wrench remember when I get like George like you you
don't have one here because you fucking went crazy when I had a wrench we were in
the middle of hell my friend when I had a wrench that's when Allied master
computer Q all coming at him
of the
I wanna lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick, lick
that drives me crazy because my mom used to do that shit when I was young like you did that and I
didn't and she was like you did and I was like yo that almost will make you crazy right so I could
deal with that and now it's happening on this panel it happened today with Christine Christine came
up here somebody was doxing whoever and she was like Alex stop your crap well Alex what I'm not
Alice and then you understand and then she comes on the panel like Alex is doxing this and that bitch
I'm working. I haven't been on this panel all day
Bitch I haven't been up here all day
i look on the phone and i hear christine like stop your crap stop your crap that's what drives me
nuts it brings me back to being a kid when your mom would say that stop your crap like
bitch i didn't do it i didn't do that let's stop it i know you like what that drives me
If I did it
Like Alex stop your crap stop doxing this type of okay cool fuck you but but yo don't ever try to fucking say
I'm doing something. I'm not
That drives me crazier than anything on the planet. That is my pet peeve
And Christine did it today, once again.
Who there was an amber dunking in the chat
saying, I'm Alice's boyfriend.
I have no idea who that was.
I ducked summer like four days ago, right?
I admit to that.
Yeah, I went crazy.
So someone rang with it today and Christine,
no, hold on, but Christine says it's me
and it's not and that drives me insane.
and that's what i'm gonna come up and fucking put you in the grave you old bitch
i don't do you a bitch you old bitch the gordon alex gordon alex hello
old bitch driving fucking talking that slander you know hold on psyche that is slander by the way
So she's out here
All right, good knows that name don't fucking lie
I'm not lying. You are. Nobody else knew that I had a doctor the other day. Today, I had nothing to do with that.
That mirror and that other person that was not me. Bullshit. Bullshit? Prove it.
That's what drives me crazy. That's what my mom used to say. And it's not. I'm insane.
You are the winner!
It's not me. It wasn't me in the fucking name. No
It's all good
why
No, where he lives if I did I would even box him anyway
Well, you know something people have gone to his house, and he hides under his bed. Oh
I believe that how many pisses is that too?
I mean, it's not planters doxing though, Brian is doxing. I bet he's yeah, I know
People's names
Sure
I know right now I take a little fucking how many licks does it get to Christine's asshole nine
All right, I know I don't think that's the right Joe. I'm married. There's only one man
that's all I'm gonna do is get to your husband's ass
I say sick
oh my god
I'm just gonna say that was good
nice to see you babe
I know you're good
your husband's a lucky man
that's what I was
I'll end it with this
40 years baby
40 years
Well, I'm gonna marry psyche tomorrow. Will you come to our wedding or absolutely? Absolutely. Yeah
She's married. She said you're married or no, no, I'm married
I'll come to yours, but I'm gonna marry Joe who you marry Joe Joe's marrying you
The one drop good times
Just show guns on my he knows you wasn't supposed to show guns these show guns, okay
No, I'm nobody's puppet Alexander. I am my own
Look at me now you are a fucking puppet not not
You see summer anywhere around here. I speak for myself
Well, I protect my friend
100% Joe as you should protect your friend. I
Don't have any friends. This is YouTube. I do like well. I have summer as a real life friend
Well page is my real friend. That's a friend of me and that's fine. He's a beautiful person
I never said she's beautiful. I love her attitude. It ain't about her looks. No, I
did. I don't mean books. I as a beautiful person doesn't mean work. Thank you.
She has a beautiful person. It doesn't mean looks. What the hell did you just call
me? What did you just call me, Christine?
I
How do you just call me?
She just called me an asshole. No, I didn't
No, you're hearing things
She just fucking Joe have you taken your psychiatric medication Joe, I really didn't I don't call anybody in asshole
Not out of my mouth sweetheart, I might have called just sweetheart or a baby doll, but that's about it
well, oh my god, that's my verbiage
All I know is if anybody attacks my friend psyche, I'm gonna attack them back psyche's a real foul
You know, I have never ever
Well, maybe one time. I have never attacked psyche. I try to protect him. Yeah, you've never attacked me
No, I try to protect you. Thank you. Yeah, I do feel it
That loving that loving my energy when I was reading about the civil war because the day's the anniversary of picking charge
I was like, I wish I had a musket and I could shove it up psych's ass and put a little powder
That's a romantic joke, please that's disgusting. No, all right. I apologize
You ready to go to bed Joe? You're telling you're getting kind of Alexander. This is exactly why you were
And I've already spoke with like about it
We're concerned to you
You see the bullshit in the back psych with him. Yeah
You're right, let me see what we got
the
that's one time too many Chrissy no fuck you back chat. You don't know Alex. I know it's you don't talk to Chrissy
Guys good times is back. Should we look good times on? What do you think what do you think should we look good times on?
Oh my god good times is having a big party. Yeah
Yeah, tomorrow is this concert. Yes
Everybody get in their selling tickets at the at the event if you need them still
Um
Because he chose to do a Pew Pew 9 millimeter today on somebody else
I can't protect you if you don't protect yourself sweetheart. I know but it's a but then you're like you're like making the joke again about his
barbecue I thought was kind of funny and then
He was really having a concert I wouldn't even fucking go to good times. I know
Sometimes
We are but let me please finish baby. Yes, please. I'm sorry
But he's having a concert tomorrow for Fortress of July on Friday, and it's like cotton candy tattoo artists like people be swallowing swords.
It's like a whole fucking thing.
You just want to go I know there's a fucking view of a moon bouncy house. There's gonna be fucking face painters
I'm pretty sure Oz beyond born is going to be there. I'm pretty fucking sure. I think he said he was okay
You know what I gotta say to Christine
Don't a fucking
Taylor Swift a special performance who else you know Beyonce is gonna be a fun time
Everybody's gonna be there. Can you know we all actually did just show we know why he would have fun that idiot
He would actually probably like it like oh
Yeah, no one's gonna come
Not one person
No, but we're a fun group
Yeah, we'd be fun
But yeah, no one can make it over guys. We already got a tablecloth. Look. It's like he's sure
I mean, it's already a fucking checkerboard. It's like what the fuck the else you want you fucking animal
Bye, ciao.
I'm just kidding. I'm fucking buzzing my ass off. I'm just making fun. It's like shirt. Like oh
It's called good stock. Okay. Good stock. It's gonna be a great event. I think of it. I'm the first one to say good stock
I don't care what am I things? I'm the first one to fucking take it back. Fuck you Tom. Sorry, you know
I said a bunch of guys who's no who's going it like RCP to the the chat
Let me give you ten minutes to read Brian King's whole paragraph
Before you read that first
Can they say something for you? Read that first. Brian, money got a strike for somebody who had a
lighter that looked like a pew pew and he got a strike for it. So it is against
terms of service. Hate to break that news to you. Go ahead. Go on. Sorry. Hate to break it to
your chatter, but Christine just puts you in your place, but
Also, people can report like they can like you can go and say oh, you know, he's like
Immediately gave him the strike it wasn't later. Yeah
Be careful. It's still lit. You can see the ember.
That's the reason I love him.
I'm going to turn my camera off, but I'm still here.
This is why I love sucky to death.
Look at the stage, guys.
I try to say once a week.
Well, I see you every day, Christine,
so you're not doing a good job at once a week.
You know, I love I love to say my home.
Fuckin' hot huckets, I see you everywhere, baby.
When I, when I, when I say my home,
the serenity in it is amazing.
Down in Georgia, you're picking out peaches.
No matter where Christine choose to be,
in my heart I'll always be there.
What the fuck is that?
Well, I'm not arguing with you.
We couldn't go live.
Money on math like what you did.
It's like a project to me.
You gotta do a huddle here.
Is that what you're saying, Jeff?
What's up, man?
Oh
We're gonna we're gonna hug it we're gonna hug it out now
We'll hang out whenever
Whenever I see you at G whenever I see you at GTs tomorrow then fucking
Yeah, I'm sorry to say but you call him good times to say GT is kind of gay like you were on GT's like
I'm depressed times because he doesn't want to have a good time
Are you gonna good stock any of you psyche?
Fuck yeah
Oh, there he is the man that the promoter himself
I'm not they either promote it you idiot
Man of the hour
Why
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
No, it's good time.
Did you see him trying to change your life?
He's threatening to call the Pope Oh.
the
and I'm going to go and I'm
3rd of July. Yeah, happy 4th of July guys for sure independence day
We hate singing good times one time singing was on good times panel like I love you, man
Then he went to like beat it's like oh good
I was actually
I know another channel like I like today. I went on like, you know, I was watching Sam as and then you know
Sometimes the chats talking about me and stuff. Oh, here's Sam. I remember because it does
My nigga Joe in the building
Go away Sam and you
Sam is cool. I like said man. I don't fucking know you man
I know you love me. They always says you heard me like no, I didn't hear you idiots
You just like diamond, right Joe
No, I just want you to turn your camera on oh, that's right
See me and won't cuz he's a fucking wearing a white beater to buy a shit things on it
He's wearing a white beater
Look at good
Man would even turn his camera on a good time says cameras the fuck I'm seven
There was one time that Sam-Man got clipped having his camera on and he's like wearing a white Peter
fucking idiot. You can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk, you can't talk,
We're like man tits and a big old beer belly like Sam-Man show your fucking self you bum
We use care boy
You don't want to see my belly I'm not gonna. No, not you dumbass.
I don't want to see your belly. No, I don't actually.
Are you being weird again? I heard you being weird.
You damn maggot. Hey maggot. Hey maggot, Alex.
Talk to him, Alex. Samman's calling you out, boy.
Well, you gonna be quiet now. Bird got your teeth, boy.
Alex, hey, Megan, be careful. He's gonna drop them bibs
Oh my god. Good time. Good time. Good time. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare you. I dare
Don't even ask questions that we don't want the answer to
Go time just cook. He's drinking that daddy
You have your boy
Shut up you faggot, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up,
Let's leave our dicks out of it. Let's leave that out of it. Come on
And put a block to his head and making so my dick
What's your language?
tell me tell me one day like about three weeks ago you were live on panel in the daytime
and you left me out doing samman you ended the panel and we were in the backstage it was just me
out doing samman what's your point yeah man you gotta freak off you gotta freak off samman said
what he said what he what he said he said enough to get him put in rikers next to his boy
That's what he said.
And he doesn't know everything.
You know what he said?
Yo, as soon as you enter the site, you ask,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
I'm gonna kill you.
That's what he said.
I
The people understand it doesn't make a difference if you float it or you say
That's your boy
Time out for tonight
Good good times. Why do you why do you have a bush good times? What the fuck?
Yeah, like all got a robot voice for nine days
I know it doesn't Ryan that's why it's a professor I keep explaining and then he is like I look
We'll just all say the word you can say and any say repeats it like the same exact words like this quote
I'd say no, he doesn't get it. So he needs to go through a
I know he said he was ridiculous
You he got to pay you to come up
Oh, what I just heard that was what I just heard
Tell him how much you gotta pay you
You can't know but then he'll just like do it again. He can't help himself. It's like so I don't know
He laughs he laughs
Okay, well, he's talking about good times. He's talking about buddy
He's talking about you Joe
Say that same shit about me all the time. He's talking about where he says he says it about me too. Yeah
Oh, well exactly good. I've got a lot of mouth the niggas wear them fucking
He didn't he did it with an a come on he did it with an a
That was the wrong one he said that's wrong when he said
It sounds wrong.
It's giving you pass, man.
It's Joe, man.
White people are the ones.
Joe, Joe, Joe is racist at night.
So you gotta watch out.
I know.
Oh, Sam, man.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
Yeah, I heard the boobs.
Yo, I do eat blowny sometimes, but I
Know I'm actually eating good this weekend, but some we got yeah
So we just like I do eat a blowny sandwich, I fuck it too proud the bed man
Same fuck. Yeah. Fuck. Yeah
Are you
I'll tell you right now singing you're cool, but don't you ever talk about my boy Sam and I'll kill you right now boy
He's joking psyche. He's kidding, man
I don't care if he's kidding or not. If you're supposed to say
Psyche, what is it? It's against my rules. Okay, and he knows it and that's why I'm here kid
If you don't know it's the rules, I might not be mad, but it's like and he is and I've explained
Yes, I understand I understand I'm just saying this that I don't take offense
Oh, I mean, I just need to like, you know, I do run the show and so it's like if he doesn't then I'll just have to cut
I'm off and I don't want to I like the guy, but
With Joe I said I'm down for a little while and bring them back up
Yeah, Joe and I we had a little bit too much to drink and they're like acting like a check-out stop saying the done
Yeah, you know it got for fuck's sake. I mean, yeah, she knows like you should see people just keep doing
Oh doing doing it. I'm like, I see on other shows
Sometimes what is it? What is it same and you say to people you'd be like take a water break?
Didn't you show firearms on her show you just sit on mine
She didn't give you permission for that
Yeah, I don't think she did because
It's funny, but yeah, it wasn't pretty funny to me and
or something, that probably
will piss me off.
Yeah, but everyone's talking about that.
It's the talk of the town.
It's the biggest event of the year.
It's literally retarded.
You can see it's kind of funny when, like,
you get bothered by it.
And it's just like,
our last chance to do it
because then tomorrow when nobody comes,
they'll be like,
oh, this is a joke.
Right, so tonight,
just let her tell her fun.
Yeah, yeah, a couple things
sitting right in front of me.
Can we take this call?
Okay.
But no, no, I don't and um
Yeah, oh my gosh. Well, I was close. You know almost
Pulled out his gun. He's a couple of things sitting on the table what I'd like to see though
No, I would not like to I just explain I would not like to because they are guns
Why is he doing that? Why is he pulling out my arms, man?
Um, he's going a little because he's like feeling he's feeling threatened because he's like one of those kind of nuts
The things everyone wants to like you know, squat on his land. And so now like, you know, I'll be I'll be kind of figure that out and like, you know
the thing where he's like, oh, we're having, we're having good stock, you know, and it gets good times houses. It'd be like, you know, flame
throwers, you know, like, you know, shantugglers and people on stilts. There's gonna be midgets and, you know,
elephants, and it's like a circus, like a music circus. And it's like a, he's gonna have like, he's gonna go fund me page. It was like $100 a ticket.
I think he's made like $7,000 or something. So everyone's gonna come. No, I don't know how much he's made, but, you know, but then, um,
Yeah, so good times doesn't like he thinks oh that's gonna happen and so he takes oh so he just wants to show his guts
so to show that he's armed and to scare people away, but
I don't think it's gonna stop anybody from
city of the tents
So who made the seven thousand?
I was I think I know what I think Aldi has has the
I don't I don't know if anyone funded it, but you know, I think they're selling tickets that they're
Like last night almost there's anything. Did you did you did you see the poster?
Poster for the what?
Yeah
What it what's supposed to say? What was it?
It was like you can meet Audi 1k on like day one
It seems like it's organized Alex what are you doing Alice? You're so ridiculous Alice
Why are you backstage? Why are you screaming words that are forbidden on the show?
You're getting all upset your microphone. Do you keep turning it back up?
You're just gonna be annoying the rest of the night or I mean it's like I can't take it anymore. Hey, Katie
Alex, are you gonna be that Dave?
The IPS in the back to that it will behave or else you're not going to my phone. I'm looking in the back
Oh good times, huh
It's a good stuff will be a mass arrest event so don't even think I'm going to good times house
Well, I don't think any guys is anybody gonna go there. No
I heard about a bunch of people that fucking paid
Well, okay, yeah, so you're not yeah, I do have a paid but that's like
No, they said they have tickets and shit
The beginning refunds are they you know, if there's not a refund. Yeah, they're gonna fucking have like lawsuit
Yeah, and then
All the will be in big trouble, but I don't think would it be out of here would it be good times because it's his property
Yeah, but he would you invite the people over there? Yeah, I don't know. I don't know wait. What what happened to your whole panel?
I'm cheated out. I don't know
John everyone that
Man happy fourth. Yeah
You killed the panel JT like you kill all my panel. Oh shit. Oh
JT I want to ask you a question JT
This is like who's this mentally?
Handicap person that you and like LZ decided to go torture and like have him fly to Florida to look for his dream girl
You like sent like hookers
You made him jerk up on camera
Someone said you demanded that and he's slow, you know, he's a little bit slow.
He went to Florida to meet somebody that didn't exist, okay?
Are you and you sent him there? You told him to go?
Yes, I heard the story. Someone came on and told the whole story.
You just believe everything you hear about me? Jesus.
No, we had a whole interview about it and we collaborated or corroborated the LD aspect of it,
but I don't understand why people that are in our panel, you know, who he is.
You know, we don't do after the first time the person really can't complain especially the fifth time and when I I know
Oh, he's here
He's being heavy enough
I know he's gonna do but it's like, you know
So you're gonna you're gonna let him fuck around a little bit you like
Everyone fuck around but it's like when it goes too far, you know, it's like you can fuck around but it's like
Well, that's when you switch when it goes too far you hit the switch
Right, it's like it's like you cannot say something real quick about that situation
that that guy right there says that he's always the smartest he has he's the
highest IQ I mean do you think that that's really a high IQ if I can you
can be talked into going to Florida to meet nothing okay okay okay but he's
the autistic or someone said he has kind of like I don't have downs and reverse
it was any more serious
You don't know but you think you why would you do this the person anyway? I mean JC
Yeah, I don't know why would you do this or somebody like why did but that person do to you like what's the reasoning behind why did you would like
Do something cruel like that. Are you cruel?
How many yeah, I don't know Alice. He's one more chance tonight Alice
You know, he's he's probably to the backshot that he would behave. Okay. I don't want to okay twice me
home maybe
Hundred times. You know what some of us other times, you know, sometimes it takes a million times and sometimes, you know
It's like for what is like
It doesn't matter how many times we do something we can still change for the future, right?
It's like no matter how what we do in the past we can always change in the future
That's the whole thing about being a human and like, you know being a starting from a selfish, you know child
You know turning into like, you know adult that's supposed to be a
So basically you were talking a bunch of shit about me with like little to no context and you're confronting me about it. Why?
Oh, good turn around things on me. No, I'm asking this story because someone tells us someone tell the story
I'm asking is it true is it not and you're you seem to know what you're talking about like I don't I know what
I'm talking about so you think something must be some somewhat true
I don't think someone's gonna make up the story of no or there's too many random
First of all, who'd you hear from?
I forgot does anybody know a shot who came on and told us story the other day
Um, they came on they're like
If you don't know
I forgot I forgot who was it was some good morning if you don't remember we told you I think it was probably Tiffany, right?
Tiffany. Yeah, I think it was Tiffany. Yeah. Yeah, it was a Tiffany. Yeah. Yeah
Little history on Tiffany
the
She's not the best looking girl, you know, oh that set her off right there immediately after that
She's like I want to find out everything. I can't find out about JT. I'm gonna go around everywhere
He's ever been and I'm gonna pay people to tell me anything. They know about JT
So that kind of set the tone for me and Tiffany. She's never really been
They're really been normal ever since so it just goes around same thing with the hand
I think I told you the Hannah thing
I'm rejected rejected I rejected her became she tried to basically step into my relationship
which she knows rain and I actually live together she comes tries to get in there and do some
weird shit I read I let her I rejected her not not in a mean way I was just just rejection
what does she do she runs around everywhere she can talking as much shit as she can about
me so it's like
He was hitting on you
Yeah, fuck. Yeah, she was she thought she said that she thought rain and I were swingers
And this she it was okay for her to just try to interject
Maybe she thought you were then she's like
She was trying to cover her ass but basically what happened was rain was out of town for a little bit
She she immediately tries to start talking to me privately. I said no
I end up doing a stream yard where we're all in the backstage and you know how stream yard works
You know you can keep people in the backstage without the people on the stage knowing that right?
So I had a few people in the backstage to hear what was going on
the
that's the guy who went to Florida. Now that guy, he's been obsessed. Yeah, he's been obsessed with this thing calling itself Tessa.
It's like a catfish or something, right?
And he's been obsessed with this thing for a while now.
And so he bought, he already bought a ticket to go see them without, before I knew anything about it. So.
the
No, no, no, he the the the catfish told him to go there to meet him there
But she's not a real person. It's like a guy. I pretend to be a woman or something
We don't know who it is. Nobody knows who it is
It could be black RG. It could be fucking
Come to Florida, so why would they come to Florida?
Well, he went to Florida to meet this person, but that person lived there
But he didn't talk to them
He said the person told him to go there, but the person was to say oh come visit me and maybe they left themselves
Or anymore, how'd you guys get involved?
Okay, okay, okay, but who told him to go to but that person told me to go to Florida. Yeah
It sounds like to me that fucking he was already fucking going
And then probably JT was like, huh, you know what, I'll just fucking help steer this, you know
He was already gonna go. I said, look if tessa doesn't show up, we'll get you a prostitute
You know at least something so you're like sending we are sending money instead of you're like, you know
I would never send money. Hell no, okay
No, so you're he was taking your call or you're on his chat or what's happened? I don't understand completely like you were like
But how did you get like involved like involved in that? He just has his presence stream
He's like a little bit is he mentally retarded like I'm not sure. He's like autistic or something
But yeah